Guide to the Kermit Carlyle Parsons papers, circa 1945-1999
Parsons, Kermit Carlyle papers, circa 1945-1999
- Series II. Nathaniel Owings Archive Project
  - Baltimore
    - Stewart Bryant papers
      - Regional Planning Council - rapid transit, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 31)
      - Franklin-Mulberry Design-In, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 32)
      - Neighborhood Design Center, 1969-1974 (Box 21, Folder 33)
      - Lithuanian Tour Report (Box 21, Folder 34)
      - Sharp Street - Property Owners (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Southwest Planning Council - Research and Corporation Meetings (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Schools (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Urban Commission (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Commission on Housing and Urban Development-Baltimore Annual Conference of the United Methodist Church (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Baltimore sketch plan (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Food co-op (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Demonstration City - Model Cities (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Sierra Club, Baltimore - UDCA, Leakin Park, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - John Volpe and MAD, 1970-1972 (Box 22, Folder 10-11)
      - ECHO House (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - ECHO House - multi-purpose center (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Harbor Committee (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Historic preservation (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - Fells Point, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 16)
      - Fells Point-display (Box 22, Folder 17)
      - Fells Point, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - George Grier talk, Higher Education Council on Urban Affairs - joint development, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Rosemont hearing testimony, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 2-3)
      - Rosemont studies and correspondence (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Franklin-Mulberry correspondence, development plan, meeting minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Franklin-Mulberry public presentation, March 1969 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Lafayette Square (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Neighborhood correspondence and articles (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - East-West expressway (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - UDCA 3-A work program (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - Rosemont position paper, meeting, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - 3-A expressway (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Rosemont - correspondence, plans (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Rosemont - Schaefer (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - Rosemont neighborhood - west leg, Baltimore (Box 29, Folder 15)
      - Rosemont material [Stew Bryant], December 1968 (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - Quad Avenue industrial site (Box 29, Folder 17)
      - City Coordinating Committee minutes, notes - interstate system corridor development (Box 29, Folder 18)
      - Historic park (Box 29, Folder 19)
      - Inner Harbor bridge, educational park (Box 29, Folder 19)
      - CBD III reports, minutes - downtown Baltimore planning, 1967-1968 (Box 29, Folder 20)
      - Mayor's City Coordinating Committee - joint development (Box 29, Folder 21)
      - Leakin Park neighborhood - freeway material, survey (Box 29, Folder 22)
      - Implementation team (Box 29, Folder 23)
      - 3-A expressway - correspondence and reports, 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder 24)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1967-1970, undated (Box 22, Folder 19-24)
      - Newspaper clippings and articles (Box 22, Folder 25-26)
      - Preliminary Case Report in Compliance with Section 106 of the National Historic Preservation Act of 1966: Interstate Route 83 in the Vicinity of the Fells Point Historic District, Baltimore, Maryland. Prepared by Per Hall, Pullerits-Zollman, Joint Venture Consulting Engineers., November 1974 (Box 22, Folder 27)
      - A Preservation Index for the Federal Hill Historic District, Baltimore, Maryland. Prepared by Russell Wright and Denys P. Meyers., November 1, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 28)
      - Preliminary Case Report in Compliance with Historic Preservation Act 106: Interstate Route 83 in the Vicinity of St. Vincent De Paul Roman Catholic Church, Shot Tower, Caton-Carroll Mansion, Star Spangled Banner Flag House, Baltimore, Maryland. Prepared by U.S. Dept. of Transportation-Federal Highway Administration and Maryland Dept. of Transportation-State Highway Administration., December 1974 (Box 22, Folder 29)
      - Informational Report for Compliance with Section 106 of the National Historic Preservation Act of 1966: Boulevard Ring in the Vicinity of the Federal Hill Historic District, Baltimore, Maryland. Prepared by Rummel, Klepper and Kahl, Consulting Engineers., February 1974 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Preliminary Case Report, Historic Preservation Act, Section 106: Interstate Route 95 in the Vicinity of Fort McHenry National Historic Shrine, Baltimore, Maryland. Prepared by Per Hall, Pullerits-Zollman (Joint Venture), May 1974 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Sample: Baltimore Urban Renewal and Housing Agency (BURHA) bidding procedure (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Steuart Hill code enforcement (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - "Baltimore Plans," Baltimore Planning Commission newsletter, 1967-1969 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - AIA, AIP - Baltimore and San Francisco (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - AIA, AIP - Non-Baltimore (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Newark, New Jersey (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, reports and plans (unsorted) (Box 23, Folder 9-12)
      - Correspondence, press releases, public law copies, 1968-1970 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - European trip report from Real Estate Research Corporation, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - AIP-Baltimore and National (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - AIP-Baltimore chapter, 1967-1968. 1970 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - AIP-Urban Esthetics Committee (Baltimore), 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - AIP newsletters, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - Crosstown Community, Philadelphia (historical reading material) (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - Baltimore Urban Design Work outline (Box 23, Folder 20)
      - Land use changes along expressways (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - articles on planning, UDCA (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Development Design Manual (Baltimore project) - Stewart Bryant (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - Pratt correspondence-Wilbur Smith and Associates - Traffic data (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - UDCT progress reports, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 25)
      - Urban design reports (Box 23, Folder 26)
      - Planners for Equal Opportunity, 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 27)
      - Bureau of Public Roads, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Land use control at interchanges (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Continuing planning process - social and economic survey manuals, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Parkways, scenic highways - federal, state, regional (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Replacement legislation, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - SOM-San Francisco (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Bay Area Neighborhood Development - San Francisco (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Urban Design Committee, AIP, 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - The Overview Group, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Baltimore Concept Team - planning process (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - California Div. of Highways - right of way interim use, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Urban Design Committee, AIP (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Political process, highway problems - Ken Geiser, MIT (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Highway Research Board - roadside development, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous San Francisco (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Washington AIP Conference (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Emergency Committee on the Transportation Crisis, Washington D.C., 1968 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - Cross-town expressway, Philadelphia, 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Federal regulations (BPR), 1969 (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - BPR hearing regulations, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - Newark, New Jersey (Box 24, Folder 21)
      - Bridwell - Systems Design Corporation - concept team (Box 24, Folder 22)
      - Air rights development, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 23)
      - Traffic estimation courses, procedures (Box 24, Folder 24)
      - Town meeting (advocacy planning) (Box 24, Folder 25)
      - Land use and traffic generation (Box 24, Folder 26)
      - Federal aid - freeway corridor improvement programs (Box 24, Folder 27)
      - AIP - minority affairs (Box 24, Folder 28)
      - Multiple Use of Lands within Highway Rights-of-Way. Barton-Aschman Associates., 1968 (Box 24, Folder 29)
      - Highways and Urban Development: Report on the Second National Conference, Williamsburg, Va. American Association of State Highway Officials.; National Association of Counties.; National League of Cities., 1966 (Box 24, Folder 30)
      - A Report on the Status of Multiple Use and Joint Development. Prepared by Environmental Development Division, Office of Right-of-Way and Location, Bureau of Public Roads, September 30, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 31)
      - Planning Action for Equal Opportunity. Planners for Equal Opportunity first annual conference. Conference proceedings., December 10, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 32)
      - Selections from "Study of the Effect, If Any, of an Urban Freeway Upon Residential Properties Contiguous to the Right of Way." David C. Colony, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 33)
      - Summary Review of Major Metropolitan Area Transportation Studies in the United States. Richard M. Zettel and Richard R. Carll, November 1962 (Box 24, Folder 34)
      - Urbanized Area Transportation Study: Population, Economic, and Land Use Forecast Techniques. Illinois Division of Highways, Bureau of Planning., 1965 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Photographs
      - Aerial photo of Baltimore Interstate Highway System 3-A (Mapcase-folder 1)
      - Baltimore/downtown, Inner Harbor (Box 32, Folder 28)
      - Baltimore/Fells Point, Inner Harbor (Box 32, Folder 29)
      - Baltimore images - Fells Point, view from Federal Hall, Allied Chemical site (Box 32, Folder 30)
      - SOM slides - Dallas (Box 32, Folder 31)
      - SOM slides - Seattle (Box 32, Folder 32)
      - SOM slides - Pittsburgh (Box 32, Folder 33)
      - SOM slides - West Side Highway, New York City (Box 32, Folder 34)
      - SOM slides - Baltimore (Box 32, Folder 35)
      - SOM slides - Atlanta (Box 32, Folder 36)
      - SOM slides - Denver/Chicago (Box 32, Folder 37)
      - SOM slides - Signage and Graphics (Box 32, Folder 38)
      - SOM slides - Urban Design Process (Box 32, Folder 39)
      - SOM slides - Miscellaneous Freeway Infrastructure (Box 32, Folder 40)
      - SOM negatives and contact sheets - Fells Point (Box 32, Folder 41)
      - SOM negatives and contact sheets - Franklin/Mulberry (Box 32, Folder 42)
      - SOM negatives and contact sheets - UDCA (Box 32, Folder 43)
      - Georgetown; Union Station; Fort Meade [negatives] (Box 32, Folder 44)
      - SOM 139-74194 [negatives] (Box 33)
      - SOM 101-503 - Baltimore Neighborhoods [negatives] (Box 33)
      - SOM 101-220 - Baltimore Neighborhoods [contact sheets] (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - SOM 221-503 - Baltimore Neighborhoods [contact sheets] (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - SOM negatives and contact sheets - miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Baltimore - Inner Harbor slides (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Slides, Owings show (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Slides, Joint Development Transit Study (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Slides, miscellaneous highway and transit images (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Baltimore Freeways slides - Miscellaneous neighborhood information (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Baltimore Freeways slides - BOD Show (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Baltimore Freeways slides - Study Model (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Baltimore Freeways slides - Concepts and Studies (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Baltimore Freeways slides - Housing and Joint Development (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Baltimore Freeways slides - City Views (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - Baltimore Freeways slides - Harbor Views (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - Baltimore Freeways slides - SRC (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Baltimore Freeways slides - miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Baltimore Freeways slides (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Baltimore slides (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - Baltimore slides - Baltimore Graphics (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - 1967 System slides (Box 33, Folder 20)
      - 1967 System slides - Rosemont (Box 33, Folder 21)
      - 1967 System slides - Leakin Park (Box 33, Folder 22)
      - 1967 System slides - Franklin/Mulberry (Box 33, Folder 23)
      - Baltimore Freeway slides - Northeast (Box 33, Folder 24)
      - Baltimore Harbor slides, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 25)
      - Baltimore Inner Harbor slides (Box 33, Folder 26)
      - Miscellaneous Baltimore slides, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 27)
      - Rosemont photo essay (Box 34)
      - Corridor photos - east, west, Leakin Park (Box 34)
      - Negatives - visual survey, aerials (Box 34)
      - Central photo file for Baltimore (Box 34)
      - Baltimore 35mm contact prints (Box 34)
      - Washington, D.C. slides, by Charles Vincent McDonald photography (Box 34)
    - Audio Recordings
      - Book dictation, interviews [mini audio cassettes] (Box 46)
      - PADC Board Meeting (Box 46)
      - Richards/Owings/Parsons interviews (Box 46)
      - Stewart Bryant interview (Box 46)
      - John Weese interview (Box 46)
      - SOM interview recording - Hopkinson, Netsch, Parsons, Smith, May 26, 1980 (Box 47)
      - SOM interview transcription - Hopkinson, Netsch, Parsons, Smith, May 26, 1980 (Box 47)
      - SOM interview recording - Hopkinson, Netsch, Parsons, Smith, Owings, Bridewell, May 26, 1980 (Box 47)
      - SOM interview transcription - Hopkinson, Netsch, Parsons, Smith, Owings, Bridewell, May 26, 1980 (Box 47)
      - SOM interview recording - Owings, Bridewell, Parsons, Gottemuller, May 27, 1980 (Box 47)
      - SOM interview transcription - Owings, Bridewell, Parsons, Gottemuller, May 27, 1980 (Box 47)
      - SOM interview recording - Hopkinson, Gottemuller, May 27, 1980 (Box 47)
      - SOM interview recording - Rogers, Trainor, May 27-28, 1980 (Box 47)
      - SOM interview recording - Rogers, May 28, 1980 (Box 47)
      - SOM interview recording - Gottemuller, May 28, 1980 (Box 47)
      - SOM interview recording - Chadin, June 19, 1980 (Box 47)
      - Magnabelt tape [unidentified] (Box 47)
  - Other Projects
    - Chicago
      - Chicago Research notes (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - SOM project general research (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Lake Meadows research (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - SOM project accounting and correspondence (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Chicago housing, SOM, Chicago Housing Authority, 2-16 and 2-19, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Chicago housing, SOM, Chicago Housing Authority, Ogden Courts (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Chicago, Lake Meadows, SOM records, June 1948-June 1950 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Chicago, Lake Meadows, SOM correspondence, July 1950-June 1951 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Chicago, Lake Meadows, SOM correspondence, July 1951-December 1952 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Chicago, Lake Meadows, SOM records, 1954-1959 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Chicago, Lake Meadows, SOM records-miscellaneous (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Chicago, Lake Meadows, SOM records, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Chicago, Lake Meadows, Chicago Memorial Hospital (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Chicago, Lake Meadows, Court cases (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - Chicago, Lake Meadows, Relocation (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Chicago, Lake Meadows, Olivet Baptist Church (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - Chicago, Lake Meadows, Chicago Land Clearance Commission (CLCC) proceedings (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - Chicago, Lake Meadows, CLCC schedules, 1953-1954 (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - Chicago, Lake Meadows, City Council proceedings (Box 38, Folder 19)
      - Chicago, Ft. Dearborn, July-December 1954 (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - Chicago, Lake Meadows, Chicago Plan Commission proceedings (Box 38, Folder 21)
      - Chicago, Pettibone papers, 1944-1946 (Box 38, Folder 22)
      - Chicago, Pettibone papers, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 23)
      - Chicago, Pettibone papers, 1948-1951 (Box 38, Folder 24)
      - Chicago, Ft. Dearborn, 1947-June 1954 (Box 38, Folder 25)
      - Chicago, Ft. Dearborn, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 26)
      - Chicago, Ft. Dearborn, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 27)
      - Chicago, Ft. Dearborn, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 28)
      - Chicago, Ft. Dearborn, 1958-1962 (Box 38, Folder 29)
      - "Community Appraisal Study: A Summary of Current Proposals." Southside Planning Board, Spring 1952 (Box 38, Folder 30)
      - Chicago Plan Commission, South Central area report, 1950 (Box 38, Folder 31)
      - Chicago Greyhound Bus Terminal, 1949-1953 (Box 38, Folder 32)
      - Chicago notes, 1980 (Box 39)
      - The Fort Dearborn Project: A New Forntier for Downtown Chicago. Prepared by the Fort Dearborn Project Team., June 1956 (Box 39)
    - Washington, D.C.
      - Pennsylvania Ave. Redevelopment Corp. correspondence/reports (Owings project) (Box 39)
      - Pennsylvania Ave. Redevelopment Corp. Brochure (Box 39)
      - Pennsylvania Ave. Redevelopment Corp. Official Chronology (Box 39)
      - Nathianiel Alexander Owings and the Plan for Pennsylvania Avenue. Vong Hin Yap, 1983 (Box 39)
      - Minnesota Avenue Joint Development Study. Robert J. Harmon and Associates, Inc. Prepared for the Office of Planning and Development of the Government of the District of Columbia., December 1981 (Box 39)
      - Federal City Bicentennial Development Corporation Files, 1969-1970 (Box 39)
      - The Joint Development of Housing & Freeways. Prepared by the Department of Highway and Traffic - District of Columbia., February 1967 (Box 41)
    - Oak Ridge, Tennessee
      - Master Plan - Oak Ridge, Tennessee. Prepared by SOM., December 1948 (Box 39)
      - Oak Ridge, Tennessee articles (Box 39)
      - Oak Ridge, Tennessee project photographs (Box 39)
    - Monterey Coast (California)
      - SOM correspondence, reports - Monterey Coast, Big Sur, late 1950s - early 1970s (Box 39)
      - California articles - Monterey Coast (Box 39)
      - The California Tomorrow Plan - A First Sketch, 1971 (Box 39)
      - Correspondence and reports, 1956-1960 (Box 39)
      - Correspondence and reports, 1961-1964 (Box 39)
      - Owings correspondence prior to Monterey Master Plan Project, 1959-1960 (Box 39)
      - Owings correspondence, 1960 (Box 39)
      - Owings correspondence, January 1961 - June 1962 (Box 39)
      - Owings correspondence, July 1962-1967 (Box 39)
      - Monterey Coast Scenic Conservation Area Ordinance (Box 39)
      - Reports, memoranda, legal documents (Box 39)
      - Proposed Master Plan of Land Use for the Monterey County Coast Area., November 10, 1961 (Box 39)
      - Monterey Coastal Area Master Plan, Summary (Preliminary). Prepared by SOM., July 1960 (Box 39)
      - Monterey Coast Master Plan, Section I. Prepared by SOM., October 1960 (Box 39)
      - Monterey Coast Master Plan, Section II. Prepared by SOM., October 1960 (Box 39)
      - Proposals for a Coast Master Plan - County of Monterey. Prepared by the Citizens Coast Committee., November 14, 1961 (Box 39)
      - Improving the Scenic Coast Route. Prepared by the Monterey County Planning Commission, July 1959 (Box 39)
      - California North Coast Survey. Prepared by the CA Division of Beaches and Parks, the CA Dept. of Public Works, the Sierra Club, the wildreness Society, Point Reyes National Seashore Foundation, Sunset Magainze, and the National Park Service, 1960 (Box 39)
      - Outline of Basic Plan Study: Monterey Peninsula. Progress Report. Prepared by SOM., May 14, 1957 (Box 39)
      - Commercial Survey for the Del Monte Properties Company. Prepared by SOM., January 1954 (Box 39)
      - Rental Housing Survey - Analysis of First Phase. Prepared by SOM. (Box 39)
      - Del Monte Shopping Center Design Scheme. Prepared by SOM, Gardner A. Daily, and Associated Architects. (Box 39)
      - SOM Family Dwelling Model photographs (Box 39)
      - Miscellaneous aerial photographs, October 2, 1959 (Box 39)
    - San Francisco, California
      - San Francisco news articles and correspondence (Box 40)
      - Golden Gateway Urban Renewal Project - articles and correspondence (Box 40)
      - San Francisco Redevelopment Area E: A Report and General Development Plan. Prepared by SOM., June-July 1948 (Box 40)
      - The Tentative Plan for the Embarcadero-Lower Market Redevelopment Project E-I. Prepared by SOM, July 3, 1958 (Box 40)
      - San Francisco Civic Center Development Plan, Preliminary Report. Prepared by Wurster, Bernardi, and Emmons, SOM, and DeLeuw, Cather & Co., July 31 ,1957 (Box 40)
      - Site Feasibility Study for San Francisco. Prepared by SOM. (Box 40)
      - Architect Advisory Panel Evaluation Report - Redevelopment of the Golden Gateway. Prepared by the San Francisco Redevelopment Agency., August 1, 1960 (Box 40)
      - Architect Engineers Report on Study of Embarcadero Plaza and Depressed Freeway Plan. Prepared by SOM. (Box 40)
      - Proposal for An Economic, Engineering, and Architectural Study of the Modernization of the Port of San Francisco. Prepared by SOM., January 14, 1959 (Box 40)
      - Modernizing Downtown San Francisco. Prepared by San Francisco Department of City Planning, January 1955 (Box 40)
      - Housing and Neighborhood Conditions in San Francisco. Prepared by San Francisco Department of City Planning, September 1955 (Box 40)
      - Proposed Housing Program for the Bunker Hill Company, Kellogg, Idaho, March 1956 (Box 40)
      - SOM - San Francisco Office Procedure Guide (Box 40)
      - San Francisco Civic Center Development Plan: Space Requirements - City and County Offices. Prepared by Wurster, Bernardi, and Emmons, SOM, And DeLeus, Cather & Co., May 7, 1957 (Box 41)
      - The Golden Gateway - General Development Plan for Redevelopment Area E. Prepared by SOM. (Box 41)
      - The San Francisco Civic Center Development Plan. Prepared by Wurster, Bernardi and Emmons, SOM, and DeLeuw, Cather & Co., October 15, 1958 (Box 41)
      - The Golden Gateway Redevelopment Plan - Excerpts from SOM Report. Prepared by the San Francisco City Planning Commission and the Redevelopment Authority., September 1957 (Box 41)
      - The Golden Gateway: A proposal to the Redevelopment Agency of the Public Garage and Residential Areas of Project Area E-1 in San Francisco. Prepared by the Golden Gateway Center. (Box 41)
    - Other Publications
      - Center City Transportation Project: Summary Report. Prepared by Arthur D. Little, Inc., SOM, RERC, and Wilbur Smith and Associates., September 1970 (Box 40)
      - Center City Transportation Project: Dallas. Prepared by Arthur D. Little, Inc., SOM, RERC, and Wilbur Smith and Associates., September 1970 (Box 40)
      - Center City Transportation Project: Atlanta. Prepared by Arthur D. Little, Inc., SOM, RERC, and Wilbur Smith and Associates., September 1970 (Box 40)
      - Center City Transportation Project: Denver. Prepared by Arthur D. Little, Inc., SOM, RERC, and Wilbur Smith and Associates., September 1970 (Box 40)
      - Center City Transportation Project: Pittsburgh. Prepared by Arthur D. Little, Inc., SOM, RERC, and Wilbur Smith and Associates., September 1970 (Box 40)
      - Center City Transportation Project: Seattle. Prepared by Arthur D. Little, Inc., SOM, RERC, and Wilbur Smith and Associates., September 1970 (Box 40)
      - Center City Transportation Project: Institutional Strategies for Urban Transportation. Prepared by RERC., September 1970 (Box 40)
      - Center City Transportation Project: Financing Public Transportation. Arthur D. Little, Inc., September 1970 (Box 40)
      - Center City Transportation Project: Consumer Analysis Guideline. Arthur D. Little, Inc., September 1970 (Box 40)
      - Study and Evaluation of Various Types of Pre-Fabricated Housing. Prepared by SOM., November 29, 1949 (Box 40)
      - SOM Services Brochure - Version I (Box 40)
      - SOM Services Brochure - Version II (Box 40)
      - Land Use and Transportation Report (Box 40)